SHUBHASH JHA

Software Engineer

Address:

I -202, Madhav Homes, Vastral, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India -

Mo: +91 7359516990 / +91 8511995337

Email Id: shubhash.career@gmail.com



Career Objective

Searching for a challenging position as a software engineer to utilise my tech and design skills for software program development, testing and quality management. My Aim is to become Specialised in the software development Industry in four to five Years.

Language

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

August 2020 -November 2020 Company:

Ansi ByteCode LLP

Trainee Software Engineer

- Developed UI based Desktop application using DevExpress tool.
- · Worked on Console Applications.
- Documentation Preparation for teams.

Work Experience

December 2020 -April 2023

LLP

Company:

Xcode web Solutions

Software Engineer

- · Working in New development and maintain client products.
- Taking a requirement from client, understand the flow, and development with the teams.
- Communication with Client.

April 2023 - Current*

Software Engineer

Company: eClinicalWorks Pvt Ltd.

- · Working on Live Product. Introduce new features in Existing
- · Communicate with QA & PA Team for taking requirement.
- · Worked on Product Security stuff.
- Maintain DS/FS documents for Implemented Feature in Product.

Education

2016 - 2020

GTU

B.E. (Computer Engineering)

Result: 8.44 / 10 CGPA (Apollo Institutes of Engineering

JavaScript

and Technology)

2014 - 2016 GSEB

HSC (Science Stream)

Result: 67 % (Vivekananda high School)

Skills

Technical skills:

HTML CSS AngularJS JQuery

Angular .NET Core .NET Framework .NET

ADO.NET LINQ TypeScript C# Azure

Azure services Azure 360 Logic Apps

Web Forms AzureDevOps **Azure Functions** Basic of React Js

Database: SQL Server

os: Windows & Linux

Visual Studio SonarQube Tools: Postman

VS Code Swagger **Jenkins** Source Tree Trello Bitbucket AzureDevOps Jira Contrast

Projects

TAG

(Company: Xcode web solutions)

· Working in new development and maintenance projects, taking a requirement from a client, understanding the flow, and development with the teams. Integrated third party Applications like Xero, ActiveCampaign, JustCall Schedule publishing the Applications.

· Technology:

ASP.NET MVC (Framework), C#, ANGULARJS, SQL Server

Link: https://tradealliance.com.au/

Auxcon

(Company: Xcode web solutions)

• Implemented Redis Caching.Implemented new screens using Angular. Build Azure functions for Automation process. Schedule publishing the Applications.

Technology:

ASP.NET MVC (CORE),C#, ANGULAR,SQL Server, Azure

Link: https://www.auxcon.co.za/

IQ Academy

(Company : Xcode web solutions)

• Implemented Logic App based on client requirement.

Technology:

Azure 360 Logic Apps

Link: https://www.iqacademy.ac.za/

Abacus Insurance

- Implemented Logic Apps and Azure functions based on client requirements for validate claims/ Policies.
- (Company : Xcode web solutions) . Give support in Front end Implementation.
 - Technology:

Azure Function, .Net Core,C#, React

Link: https://www.abacus-insurance.co.za/

CRM Portal Jay Chemical Industries Limited (Freelancing)

- Implemented Front end in angular with Ag-Grid and dev-Express UI tool.
- Support on API side which is in .net framework (C#) MVC
- Technology :

.Net Framework (MVC) ,SQL Server ,C#, Angular

HMIS eClinicalWorks Pvt. Ltd.

- Worked on new requirement in existing eCW product.
- Support on API side which is in .net framework (C#) MVC
- Technology:

.Net Framework (MVC) ,SQL Server ,C#, Web Forms SonarQube, Contrast

(Academic Project)

- Online Cab Booking Services Documentation Preparation. Implemented web based applications for Cab booking system with User and Admin module. Integrated Bing Map.
 - Technology:

ASP.NET MVC (Framework), C#, SQL Server, JQuery

- · Coordinate Technical fest event in 2018 organized by Gujarat Technical University.
- · Campus Ambassador representative for CDAC (Pune) in GTU regarding Super Computer.
- Certifications from online platforms like Udemy, Coursera.

Research Paper

 Published research paper on "Structures & Communication of QR Code" in IJSRD Journal.

Link: http://ijsrd.com/Article.php?manuscript=IJSRDV8I50012

Internship

· Completed one year of Internship in SilverTouch TechLab, Ahmedabad during bachelors in final year (ASP.NET MVC).

Personal Details

Extra Curricular

Activities

 Father Name : Lalan M.Jha Birth Of Date : 09th Dec,1998 Birth Of Place : Bihar (India) • Married Status : Single

 Nationality : Indian

 Hobbies : Cricket, Traveling, Solving real world Problems